const data = [
{
    question: "Ihumoana",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Mouth of the sea", "Sea mouth", "Eyes of the sea"],
    correctAnswer: "Nose into the sea",
},
{
    question: "Kaiaua",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Eating a fish", "Eating a bird", "Eating a meal"],
    correctAnswer: "Eating mullets",
},
{ 
    question: "Ararua", 
    incorrectAnswers: ["Crossroads", "Two streams", "Long path"],
    correctAnswer: "Two paths" 
},
{
    question: "Awaiti", 
    incorrectAnswers: ["Long river", "Big river", "River of the sea"], 
    correctAnswer: "Little river" 
},
{
    question: "Arapito",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Path of the climbing plant", "Start of the path", "Road walked down"],
    correctAnswer: "End of the path",
},
{
    question: "Kaimiro",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Berry Foraging","Eating fruit","Eating seafood"],
    correctAnswer: "Eat miro berries",
},
{
    question: "Awapuni",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Blocked path", "Sacred stream", "Side creek"],
    correctAnswer: "Blocked-up river",
},
{ 
    question: "Awakino", 
    incorrectAnswers: ["Scray Creek", "Long creek", "Big creek"],
    correctAnswer: "Bad creek" 
},
{ 
    question: "Kaharoa", 
    incorrectAnswers: ["Fishing pole", "Fish hook", "Small net"], 
    correctAnswer: "Large net" 
},
{
    question: "Kaihiku",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Eating some beef", "Eating a bid", "Eating some fruit"],
    correctAnswer: "Eating a fish tail",
},
{ question: "Kairaki", 
incorrectAnswers: ["Snake eater", "Eating fruit", "Drinking water" ], 
correctAnswer: "Sky eater" 
},
{
    question: "Kaipuke",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Fish", "Bird", "Seafood"],
    correctAnswer: "Ship (wave eater)",
},
{ 
    question: "Kaipūpū", 
    incorrectAnswers: ["Eating an orange", "Eating a fish", "Eating a bird"], 
    correctAnswer: "Eat shellfish" 
},
{ 
    question: "Hukanui", 
    incorrectAnswers: ["Heavy rain", "Strong wind", "Hot sun"], 
    correctAnswer: "Heavy snow" 
},
{
    question: "Awakeri",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Creek", "River", "Stream"],
    correctAnswer: "Ditch or trench",
},
{ 
    question: "Awatuna", 
    incorrectAnswers: ["Fishing spot", "Swimming spot", "Fishing creek"], 
    correctAnswer: "Eel stream" 
},
{ 
    question: "Hiwinui", 
    incorrectAnswers: ["Cliffside", "Hilltop", "Mountain top"], 
    correctAnswer: "Big ridge" 
},
{ 
    question: "Aranui", 
    incorrectAnswers: ["Large stream", "Long River", "Dusty trail"], 
    correctAnswer: "Great pathway" 
},
{ 
    question: "Kaimangō", 
    incorrectAnswers: ["Eating a fish", "Eating a bird", "Eating a meal"], 
    correctAnswer: "Eating shark" 
},
{
    question: "Awapikopiko",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Fast river", "Deep lake", "Waterfall"],
    correctAnswer: "Winding stream",
},
];

export default data;
